Car.
Don't want to get bro
then fuck the cheves
day seventeen.
The guy who passed by said he liked it,
he liked the Chevrolet,
he liked the chevas.
Bro,
he mentioned our cool car today I'm doing my deliveries here at Centro Cara.
Oh,
I go to the caramba neighborhood to deliver 1 box of 15 mangoes,
then go to the other neighborhood and be a donkey,
right?
Mano you have to think a little bit yesterday too,
here are some deliveries that I've been doing today at the Center
and then I'll organize mano saca to make these deliveries here now.
And 1 woman asked me for her.
Go there at the store there Tal ah there's 1 good number of me employee I said,
ah it took me I'll arrive.
Cê won't believe Tamires here.
I thought she would want seventeen Passengers.
It's on,
it's already great.
So what did you say Tamires?
Seventeen little boxes,
my goodness from heaven,
seventeen little boxes
our homie brother from heaven.
I can't stand it,
I can't be scandalous that I have at the mall,
but I'm holding it like this to give 1 scream in the car.
I don't know bro,
look at this slope bro
let me give you a thank you first here good pleasure.
How many orders have you placed?
How many boxes to order?
Speaking of ten today?
This delivery thing is going well Guy
how much is the liter
make money,
take the money instead of the money being in your hand,
no money goes where it goes for gas,
you don't even have time to undertake it's not how much money you make,
it's how much money you keep,
you don't believe it,
you keep turning money and not having money.
Ah,
I understood 1 thing that is wrong with my business and tomorrow I will start.